1888articles.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy of 1888 Articles.com

**Privacy Policy Information**  
This Privacy Policy covers the 1888 Articles conduct of individual information that is provided while the articles submission. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from the users to 1888Articles.com.

**Information Collection and Use**  
1888Articles collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.  
All information collected via the Permission Request Form for copyrighted materials is used by 1888Articles.com to identify the requesting entity and respond to their request. The user's personally identifiable information is not given to third-parties.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
1888Articles.com maintains your email address and other relevant information on the premises. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside businesses. Any email notices or update announcements from 1888Articles.com will include detailed unsubscribe information, giving you the option to remove yourself from future mailings at any time.

**Cookies**  
At Present, Cookies are not used on the 1888Articles.com.

**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. 1888Articles is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 1888Articles recommends you to refer each Network Member's Privacy Statements.

**Change Notifications**  
1888Articles.com can update our Privacy Policy time to time based on our employees' and users' feedback. If there are any solid changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify through email and provide you a chance to adapt prior to any substantial change that has been taken. 1888Articles.com recommends you to often review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.
